Guide to the Steven Mallory White Papers, 1871-1901
Department of Special Collections
White, Stephen Mallory. Papers,
1871-1901
M0035
White, Stephen Mallory
30 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Correspondence and other papers relating to White's career as lawyer, Los Angeles district attorney, state senator, and U.S. Senator. Subjects covered include: estate litigation, water rights, incorporations, mortgages, property rights, local and California politics, patronage, tariffs, annexation, pensions, appeals for clemency, the Chinese problem, free silver question, Indian rights, discrimination against Catholics, Negro rights, and the Itata incident.
Administrative Information
Access
None.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the White family, 1917 and 1920.
Biography
Stephen Mallory White was born January 19, 1853 in San Francisco, California. He was a lawyer, district attorney for Los Angeles, California State Senator (1886-1890), acting Lieutenant Governor of California (1888-1890), and U.S. Senator (1893-1899). He died in Los Angeles, California, February 21, 1901.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Correspondence and other papers relating to White's career as lawyer, Los Angeles district attorney, state senator, and U.S. Senator. Subjects covered include: estate litigation, water rights, incorporations, mortgages, property rights, local and California politics, patronage, tariffs, annexation, pensions, appeals for clemency, the Chinese problem, free silver question, Indian rights, discrimination against Catholics, Negro rights, and the Itata incident.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Bierce, Ambrose, 1842-1914?.; Bradford, Gamaliel, 1863-1932.; Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925.; Daniels, Josephus, 1862-1948.; Gompers, Samuel, 1850-1924.; Griggs, John William, 1849-1927.; Hearst, William Randolph, 1863-1951.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919.; Root, Elihu, 1845-1937.; Southwick, George, 1863-1912.; Stanford, Leland, 1824-1893.; Whitehead, Charles.; Long, John Davis, 1838-1915.; Buckley, Christopher Augustine, 1845-1922.; Olney, Warren, 1841-1921.; Yellow Aster Mining and Milling Co.; Wells, Fargo & Company.; Winchell and Stanton.; Lawyers.; Democratic Party--California.; Discrimination in employment.; Silver question.; Statesmen.; Tidelands oil--California.; Patronage--California.; Itata incident.
Collection Contents
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - Subseries 1. Outgoing
    - Jan. 13, 1883 - Feb. l2, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - May 14, 1883 - Mar. 13, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - July 13, 18813- Jan. l885 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Mar. l4,1885 - Aug. 26,1886 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Sept. 29, 1886 - Jan. 7, 1888 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Feb. 9,1888 - July 27,1888 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Dec. 30, 1886 - Jan. 21, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Jan. 26, 1887 - Feb. 15, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Feb. 15, 1887 - Mar. 1, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mar. 7, 1887 - Apr. 23, 1891 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - July 27, 1888 - Nov. 5, 1888 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Nov. 5, 1888 - Mar. 11, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Jan. 8, 1889 - Mar. l5, l889 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Mar. 15, 1889 - Mar. 16, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Mar. 1889 - Aug. 13, 1889 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Aug. 14, 1889 - Jan. 11, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Jan. 11, l89O - May 30,189O (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - May 30, 1890 - Sept. 13, 1890 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Sept. 13, l890 - Jan.13,1891 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Jan. 7, 1891 - May 10, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - May 11, 1851 - Sept. 28, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - July 31, 1891 - Apr. 15, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Sept. 28, 1891 - Mar. 13, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Mar. 14, 1892- Sept. 14 1892 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Dec. 5, 1892 - Jan. 27, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Jan. 28, 1893 - Mar. 5, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Mar. 6,1893 - May 25, 1893 - Jan. 12, 13, 13 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Mar. 9, 1893 - Mar. 18, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - May lO, 1893 - Mar. 18, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - June 23, 1893 - Sept. 5, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Nov. 15, 1893 -Sept. 11,1894 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Jan. 23, 1894 - Mar. 6, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Mar. 6, 1894 - May 14, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - May 14, 1894 - July 17, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - July l7, 1894 - June 25, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Dec. 5, 1894 -Feb. 11, l895 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Feb. 11, 1895 - May 18, 1895 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - July 16, 1895 - Dec. 9, 1895 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Dec. 5, l895 - May 12, 1897 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Dec. 10, 1895 - Feb. 25, 1896 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Feb. 21, 1896 - Mar. 28, 1896 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Mar. 28, l896 - June 22, 1896 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - June 22, 1896 - Sept. 14, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Sept. l4, 1896 - Dec. 12, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Dec. 10, 1896 - Mar.~1897 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Mar. 8, 1897 - July 7, l897 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Mar. 24, 1897 - Feb. 7, 1898 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - May 8, 1897 - Dec. 21, 1898 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - May 13, 1897 - Sept. 1, 1899 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - June 30, 1897 - Oct. 12, 1897 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - June 23, 1898 - Oct. 22, 1898 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Feb. 8, 1898 - Nay 21, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - May 21, 1898 - Nov. 8, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Nov. 8, 1898 - May 23, 1899 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Loose Outgoing Correspondence1878 - 1900 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 2. Incoming
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Aaron - Barry, J.A. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Barry - Bowers, S. (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Bowers, W.D. - Butler & B miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - Cable - Chatman (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 90)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 93)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 94)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 95)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 96)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 97)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 98)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 99)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 100)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 101)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 102)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 103)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 104)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 105)
    - Cheek - Cronenwett (Box 21, Folder 106)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 107)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 108)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 109)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 110)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 111)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 112)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 113)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 114)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 115)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 116)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 117)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 118)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 119)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 120)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 121)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 122)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 123)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 124)
    - Cronin - Dunlap (Box 22, Folder 125)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 126)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 127)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 128)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 129)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 130)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 131)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 132)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 133)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 134)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 135)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 136)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 137)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 138)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 139)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 140)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 141)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 142)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 143)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 144)
    - Dunn - Fitzgerald (Box 23, Folder 145)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 146)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 147)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 148)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 149)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 150)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 151)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 152)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 153)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 154)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 155)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 156)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 157)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 158)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 159)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 160)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 161)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 162)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 163)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 164)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 165)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 166)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 167)
    - Fitzpatrick - Germain (Box 24, Folder 168)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 169)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 170)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 171)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 172)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 173)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 174)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 175)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 176)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 177)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 178)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 179)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 180)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 181)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 182)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 183)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 184)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 185)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 186)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 187)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 188)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 189)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 190)
    - German - Hampton (Box 25, Folder 191)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 192)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 193)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 194)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 195)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 196)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 197)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 198)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 199)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 200)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 201)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 202)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 203)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 204)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 205)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 206)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 207)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 208)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 209)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 210)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 211)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 212)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 213)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 214)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 215)
    - Hance - Hicks (Box 26, Folder 216)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 217)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 218)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 219)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 220)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 221)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 222)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 223)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 224)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 225)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 227)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 228)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 229)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 230)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 231)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 232)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 233)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 234)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 235)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 236)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 237)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 238)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 239)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 240)
    - Higgins - John (Box 27, Folder 241)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 242)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 243)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 244)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 245)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 246)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 247)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 248)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 249)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 250)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 251)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 252)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 253)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 254)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 255)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 256)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 259)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 261)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 262)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 264)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 265)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 266)
    - Johnson - Kutz & K miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 267)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 268)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 270)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 271)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 272)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 273)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 274)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 275)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 276)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 277)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 278)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 279)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 280)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 281)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 282)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 283)
    - L (La Vies - Lysons, J.W.) (Box 29, Folder 284)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 285)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 286)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 287)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 288)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 289)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 290)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 291)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 292)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 293)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 294)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 295)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 296)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 297)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 298)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 299)
    - MacArthur - McKinley, B.F. (Box 30, Folder 300)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 300)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 301)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 303)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 304)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 305)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 306)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 307)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 308)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 309)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 310)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 311)
    - McKinley, Ed - Monroe, Charles (Box 31, Folder 312)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 313)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 314)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 315)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 316)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 317)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 318)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 319)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 320)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 321)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 322)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 323)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 327)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 328)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 329)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 330)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 331)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 332)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 333)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 334)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 334)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 335)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 335)
    - Monroe, W. - Nixon (Box 32, Folder 336)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 336)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 337)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 338)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 339)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 340)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 341)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 342)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 343)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 344)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 345)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 346)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 347)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 348)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 349)
    - Nobile - Pettigrew (Box 33, Folder 350)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 351)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 352)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 353)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 354)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 355)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 356)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 357)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 358)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 359)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 360)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 361)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 362)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 363)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 364)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 365)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 366)
    - Pfeiffer - Richards (Box 34, Folder 367)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 368)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 369)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 370)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 371)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 372)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 373)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 374)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 375)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 376)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 377)
    - Richardson - Seymour (Box 35, Folder 378)